Finding Aid for the Reverend James M. Lawson, Jr. Papers
Special Collections Manuscripts and Rare Books
- Sermons (1981)
  Sermons – January 18, 1981 – “Do You Want Strength And Courage?”
  Sermons – February 1, 1981 – “How Do We Enter God’s Gates With Praise?”
  Sermons – February 15, 1981 – “Why Are We Here?”
  Sermons – March 4, 1981
  Sermons – March 8, 1981 – “How Much Are You Willing To Give?”
  Sermons – March 29, 1981 – “Let The Children Come To me”
  Sermons – April 5, 1981 – “Why Did Jesus Die?”
  Sermons – April 12, 1981 – “Christ’s Battle on Palm Sunday”
  Sermons – April 19, 1981 – “Who Are We?”
  Sermons – April 26, 1981 – “The Mystery Of The Resurrected Life”
  Sermons – May 17, 1981 – “We Are All Family”
  Sermons – May 24, 1981 – “Facing Your 24th Hour”
  Sermons – May 31, 1981 – Making Life High Adventure”
  Sermons – June 28, 1981 – “Let Them Come To Me”
  Sermons – July 5, 1981 – “Carrying The Yoke Of Christ”
  Sermons – July 19, 1981 – “Take Another Look: Hungering”
  Sermons – July 26, 1981 – “Take Another Look At Your Worship”
  Sermons – August 2, 1981 – “Take Another Look At What You Give”
  Sermons – August 16, 1981 – “God Works For Good”************(check)
  Sermons – August 23, 1981
  Sermons – September 13, 1981 – “Are You A Rock?”
  Sermons – September 27, 1981 – “The Parable of 3 Sons”
  Sermons – October 4, 1981 – “Forgiveness Heals”
  Sermons – November 1, 1981
  Sermons – November 8, 1981 – “Practicing Your Faith”
  Sermons – November 22, 1981- “Are Your Ready For The Surprises”
  Sermons - November 29, 1981
  Sermons – December 6, 1981 – “Imperatives of Advent”
  Sermons – December 13, 1981 – “Defeating The World In Our Time”
  Sermons – December 20, 1981 – “When Does Christmas Begin”
- Sermons (1982)
  Sermons – January 3, 1982 – “The Day That Love Was Born”
  Sermons – January 10, 1982
  Sermons – January 17, 1982 – “Today is the Day”
  Sermons – January 24, 1982 – “Immediately”
  Sermons – January 31, 1982
  Sermons – February 7, 1982
  Sermons – February 14, 1982 – “From Disaster to Dignity”
  Sermons – February 21, 1982 – “How Well Can You See?”
  Sermons – February 28, 1982 – “Confront Yourself”
  Sermons – March 7, 1982 – “Consider Yourself....I Must Consider Myself”
  Sermons – March 14, 1982 – “You Are All You Have”
  Sermons – March 21, 1982 – “Make Me A Captive Lord”
  Sermons – March 28, 1982 – “The Consecrated Cross I’ll Bear”
  Sermons – April 4, 1982
  Sermons – April 8, 1982 – “We Participate With Christ”
  Sermons – April 11, 1982 – “Why Have We Come?”
  Sermons – April 18, 1982 – “The Fellowship We Seek”
  Sermons – April 25, 1982 – “Only Those Who Obey, Truly Believe”
  Sermons – May 2, 1982 – “And So We Are”
  Sermons- May 9, 1982 – “Can We Find True Love?”
  Sermons – May 16, 1982
  Sermons – May 23, 1982 – “Making The Most of Church Membership”
  Sermons – May 30, 1982
  Sermons – June 6, 1982 – “Jesus Christ Is Lord”
  Sermons – June 20, 1982 – “Putting On The Whole Family of God”
  Sermons – June 27, 1982 – “Turning To Become Like Children”
  Sermons – July 11, 1982 – “Your Faith Makes You Whole”
  Sermons – August 1, 1982 – “I am The Living Bread”
  Sermons – August 15, 1982 – “What Makes You Unique?”
  Sermons – September 5, 1982 – “The Cross As Disciplined Living”
  Sermons – September 19, 1982
  Sermons – September 26, 1982 – “Learing God’s Way”
  Sermons – October 3, 1982 – “We Need One Another”
  Sermons – October 10, 1982
  Sermons – October 17, 1982 – “God’s Guarantee”
  Sermons – October 24, 1982 – “Peace I Give To You”
  Sermons – October 31, 1982 – “Are You There?”
  Sermons – November 7, 1982 – “Saved For Equality”
  Sermons – November 14, 1982 – “Clapping With Two Hands”
  Sermons – November 25, 1982
  Sermons – November 28, 1982 – “Getting Ready For Christmas”
  Sermons – December 5, 1982 – “What Are You Getting For Christmas”
  Sermons – December 12, 1982 – “Returning Home For Christmas”
  Sermons – December 19, 1982 – “Where is Bethlehem?”
  Sermons – December 24, 1982
  Sermons – December 26, 1982
- Church Committees (A-C) – Box 22
  - Ad Hoc Committee for the 1984 Olympic Games – 1982-1983
  - Board of Christian Social Concerns – Alcohol and Drug Concerns – n.d.
  - Board of Christian Social Concerns – Challenge & Response – n.d.
  - Board of Christian Social Concerns – Correspondence – Incoming – 1961-1968
  - Board of Christian Social Concerns – Correspondence – Outgoing – 1962
  - Board of Christian Social Concerns – Minutes - 1961
  - Board of Christian Social Concerns – Executive Minutes – 1965
  - Board of Christian Social Concerns – Vietnam – 1968
  - Central Jurisdiction of the Methodist Church – Correspondence – Incoming – 1961-1962
  - Central Jurisdiction of the Methodist Church – Minutes – 1961
  - Central Jurisdiction of the Methodist Church – Minutes – 1962
  - Central Jurisdiction of the Methodist Church – Speaks – 1962
  - Central Jurisdiction of the Methodist Church – Episcopal Address – 1964
  - Central Jurisdiction of the Methodist Church – Cincinnati Exploratory Meeting – 1962
  - Central Jurisdiction of the Methodist Church – Packet for Cincinnati Exploratory Meeting – 1962
  - Central Jurisdiction of the Methodist Church – Article by James M. Lawson titled “Where do we go from here” – 1967
  - Central Jurisdiction of the Methodist Church – Recommendations – n.d.
  - Citizens’ Advisory Committee on Student Integration – 1976
  - Citizens Concerned with Improved Police Community Relations – 1975
  - Citizens Concerned with Improved Police Community Relations – 1976
- Church Committees – (BMCR) – Box 23
  - Black Methodist for Church Renewal – First Annual Meeting – 1969
  - Black Methodist for Church Renewal – Second Annual Meeting – n.d.
  - Black Methodist for Church Renewal – Third Annual Meeting - 1970
  - Black Methodist for Church Renewal – Fourth Annual Meeting – 1971
  - Black Methodist for Church Renewal – 26th Annual Meeting – 1993
  - Black Methodist for Church Renewal – 27th Annual Meeting – 1994
  - Black Methodist for Church Renewal – 28th Annual Meeting – 1995
  - Black Methodist for Church Renewal – 4th Sunday Service – 1974
  - Black Methodist for Church Renewal – Administrative Committee Meeting – 1970
  - Black Methodist for Church Renewal – Award of Merit – 1983
  - Black Methodist for Church Renewal – BMCR Perspectives – 1979
  - Black Methodist for Church Renewal – Board of Directors’ Meeting – 1969
  - Black Methodist for Church Renewal – Board of Directors’ Meeting – 1970
  - Black Methodist for Church Renewal – Constitution and By Laws – 1969
  - Black Methodist for Church Renewal – Correspondence – Incoming - 1968-1974
  - Black Methodist for Church Renewal – Correspondence = Incoming – n.d.
  - Black Methodist for Church Renewal – Economic Development Task Force – 1970
  - Black Methodist for Church Renewal – Executive Committee Meeting – 1969
  - Black Methodist for Church Renewal – Executive Committee Meeting – 1970
  - Black Methodist for Church Renewal – Findings – n.d.
  - Black Methodist for Church Renewal – Handbook – “How to Form a Black Caucus” – 1971
  - Black Methodist for Church Renewal – Meeting – 1971
  - Black Methodist for Church Renewal – Memphis Annual Conference – 1974
  - Black Methodist for Church Renewal – Memphis Sermon – ca. 1974
  - Black Methodist for Church Renewal – Memphis Conference Platform - n.d.
  - Black Methodist for Church Renewal – Newsletter – “NOW” – 1968-1970
  - Black Methodist for Church Renewal – Newspaper Clippings – 1969
  - Black Methodist for Church Renewal – Position Paper on Merger of Black and White Annual Conferences – 1969
  - Black Methodist for Church Renewal – Ebony Prophets – Position Paper – 1981
  - Black Methodist for Church Renewal – Program Development Committee – 1970
  - Black Methodist for Church Renewal – Program to Emphasize Inclusiveness – 1994
  - Black Methodist for Church Renewal – Second Annual Southeastern Convocation – 1970
  - Black Methodist for Church Renewal – Student Caucus – n.d.
  - Black Methodist for Church Renewal – Style of Mission – ca.1969
  - Black Methodist for Church Renewal - Task Force on Higher Education – 1970
  - Black Methodist for Church Renewal – Travel Expenses – 1070
  - Black Methodist for Church Renewal – Western Jurisdiction Report of the Committee on the Episcopacy – 1983
  - Black Methodist for Church Renewal – Miscellaneous – Poster – n.d.
- Church Committees (C-G) – Box 24
  - Commission on Religion and Race – Correspondence, Proposal - 1968 establishment
  - Commission on Religion and Race – Minutes, Reports - 1969
  - Commission on Religion and Race – Reports - 1970
  - Commission on Religion and Race – Conjectures of a Black Methodist – 1970
  - Commission on Religion and Race – Reports – 1970
  - Commission on Religion and Race – Correspondence – Incoming – 1971-1980
  - Commission on Religion and Race – Minutes – 1971
  - Commission on Religion and Race – Goals and Objectives - 1981
  - Commission on Religion and Race – Newspaper Clippings – n.d.
  - Committee for Nonviolent Action – 1960-1965
  - Committee of Southern Churchmen – 1967-1969
  - General Board of Global Ministries – Annual Report – 1992
  - General Board of Global Ministries – Correspondence – Incoming – 1984-1991
  - General Board of Global Ministries – The Methodist Church in Brazil – 1990
  - General Board of Global Ministries – Randy Nugent Affair – 1981
  - General Board of Global Ministries – Randy Nugent Speech – 1983
  - General Board of Global Ministries – Report on the Institute on Religion and Democracy – 1981
  - General Board of Global Ministries – Workshop on Church Strategies – 1976
- Church Committees – (G-N) – Box 25
  - General Conference of the United Methodist Church – ‘Daily Christian Advocate’ – 1992
  - General Conference of the United Methodist Church – James M. Lawson Statement – 1960
  - General Conference of the United Methodist Church – Council on Youth Ministry – 1970
  - General Conference of the United Methodist Church – Correspondence – Incoming – 1983-1984
  - General Conference of the United Methodist Church – Commission on the Mission of the United Methodist Church – 1985
  - General Conference of the United Methodist Church – Commission on the Mission of the United Methodist Church – Report – 1988
  - General Council on Ministries – Report – 1975
  - General Council on Ministries – Report – 1982
  - General Council on Ministries – Readus Watkins Affair – 1983
  - JAPLA: Justice, Action, and Peace in Latin America – 1969-1970
  - Joint Task Force on Health and Welfare Ministries – 1971
  - National Committee of Black Churchmen – Board Meeting – 1970
  - National Committee of Black Churchmen – Newspaper Clippings – n.d.
  - National Committee of Black Churchmen – Correspondence - Incoming – 1968
  - National Committee of Black Churchmen – Newsletter – 1968
  - National Conference of Negro Methodists – Correspondence – Incoming – 1967-1968
  - National Conference of Negro Methodists – Correspondence – Outgoing – 1967-1968
  - National Conference of Negro Methodists – Newspaper Clippings – 1968
  - National Conference of Negro Methodists – Report from Cincinnati – 1968
  - National Conference of Negro Methodists – Reports, Notes – 1967-1967
- Church Committees – (N-W) – Box 26
  - National Council on Churches – Correspondence – Incoming – 1969
  - National Council on Churches – Middle East Policy Statement – 1980
  - National Council on Churches – New World Order Theme Conference - 1991
  - National Council on Churches – Newspaper Clippings – 1969
  - National Council on Churches – Prophetic Justice Unit Committee – 1991
  - National Council on Churches – Study Committee on Social Violence – 1968
  - National Council on Churches – Study Committee on Social Violence – 1969
  - National Council on Churches – Study Committee on Social Violence – 1970
  - National Council on Churches – Study Committee on Social Violence – 1971
  - Quadrennial Emphasis of the United Methodist Church – 1968-1971
  - Southern California-Arizona Annual Conference – Campus Ministry - 1975-76
  - Southern California-Arizona Annual Conference – Correspondence – Incoming – 1976
  - Southern California-Arizona Annual Conference – Newsletter – “The Joyful Noise” – 1976
  - Southern California-Arizona Annual Conference – 1976
  - United Methodist For Church Renewal – Newsletter – “Church Renewal” – 1963-1969
  - Western Jurisdictional Conference – 1982-1984`
  - Western Jurisdictional Conference - Episcopacy – 1983-1984
  - World Conference on Religion and Peace – Position Papers - 1970
- Church Committees – (W) – Box 27
  - World Council of Churches – Correspondence – Incoming – 1961-1976
  - World Council of Churches – Correspondence – Outgoing – 1961
  - World Council of Churches – Consultation on Racism – 1968
  - World Council of Churches – “Decision-Making in a Violent World” – 1973
  - World Council of Churches – International Consultation on Racism and Racial Justice – 1988
  - World Council of Churches – Violence, Nonviolence and the Struggle for Social Justice – 1972-1974
  - World Council of Churches – Third Assembly – 1961
  - World Council of Churches – Fourth Assembly – 1968
  - World Council of Churches – Sixth Assembly – 1983
  - World Council of Churches – Newspaper Clippings – 1961
- Civil Rights – General Subject Files – (A-P) – Box 43
  - Barry Goldwater – Clippings – 1964
  - Birmingham, Alabama – Clippings – 1963
  - Birmingham, Alabama – Notes – 1963
  - Black Declaration of Independence – July 3, 1970
  - Black Manifesto – 1969
  - CORE – Correspondence – Incoming – 1961 (re: Freedom Rides)
  - CORE – Correspondence – Incoming – 1962
  - Carl Broaden Case – A961-1962
  - Chapter of Book re: Civil Rights – 1976
  - Civil Rights Act of 1964 – July 1964
  - Civil Rights Workers Murders – Clippings – June-August 1964
  - Civil Rights/Segregation – Clippings – 1962-1971
  - Clippings – Community Living – 1968
  - Clippings – Freedom Rides – May 1961
  - Clippings – Freedom Rides – 1961
  - Clippings – Freedom Ridge – n.d.
  - Clippings – James M. Lawson – 1969
  - Clippings – Violence – 1968
  - Coahoma County Branch NAACP – May 25, 1963
  - Correspondence – Incoming – Freedom Ridges – 1961
  - Danville, Virginia – 1963
  - Delta Ministry – 1969
  - Issues in the Lewis M. Steel Case – January 1969
  - March on Washington – Clippings – 1963
  - Membership Application NAACP (blank) – n.d.
  - Memphis State University – Summer Community Leadership – 1969
  - James Meredith March – Clippings 1966
  - Meredith March…And Tomorrow – July 15, 1966
  - Ministers For Freedom Through Elections – 1968
  - Montgomery Improvement Association – December 1956
  - Publications – Freedom Rides - 1961
  - George Wallace – University of Alabama – Clippings – 1963
- Civil Rights – General Subject Files – (R-W) – Box 44
  - Russwurm Award – 1969
  - Shelby County Penal Farm Report – ca. 1973
  - The South and Christian Ethics – 1963
  - Southern Regional Council Reports (L-23 to L-41) – 1961-1963
  - Southern Regional Council Report – August, Georgia and Jackson State University – June 1970
  - Southern Regional Council Report – Events at Orangeburg – February 25, 1968
  - Southern Regional Council Report – Fayette County, Tennessee – October 1969
  - Southern Regional Council Report – Federal Retreat – December 1969
  - Southern Regional Council Report – In Memphis – April 28, 1968
  - Southern Regional Council Report – The Present Dilemna of the Negro – November 2, 1967
  - Southern Regional Council Report – Public Assistance in the South – November 1966
  - Southern Regional Council Report – Racial Demonstration in the Southern Federal Courts – April 1965
  - Southern Regional Council Report – Voices From the South – August 1970
  - Southern Student Organizing Committee – Correspondence – Incoming 1966
  - Southern Student Organizing Committee – Publication – “The New South Student” – November 1966
  - Southern Student Organizing Committee – Miscellaneous – 1966
  - Southern Student Organizing Committee – Papers – 1966
  - Student Non-Violence Coordinating Committee – Correspondence – Incoming – 1960
  - Student Non-Violence Coordinating Committee – Correspondence – Incoming - 1961
  - Student Non-Violence Coordinating Committee – Correspondence – Incoming – 1962
  - Student Non-Violence Coordinating Committee – Publication – “The Student Voice” – 1960-1963
  - Students for a Democratic Society – Radical Education Project – August 1, 1966
  - Tennessee Council on Human Relations – Newsletters – 1969
  - Tennessee Council on Human Relations – Reports = January – 1970
- Civil Rights – Memphis Sanitation Strike – Oral History Transcripts – Box 46
  - Oral History Transcripts
  Lucius Burch – September 3,1968
  James M. Lawson – July 1, 1968
  James M. Lawson – September 10, 1968
  James M. Lawson – September 18, 1968
  James M. Lawson – January 21, 1969 (folder 1 of 2)
  James M. Lawson – January 21, 1969 (folder 2 of 2)
  James M. Lawson – May 27, 1969
  James M. Lawson – July 21, 1969
  James M. Lawson – August 21, 1969
  James M. Lawson – September 23, 1969 (folder 1 of 2)
  James M. Lawson – September 23, 1968 (folder 2 of 2)
  James M. Lawson – September 24, 1969 (folder 1 of 2)
  James M. Lawson – September 24, 1969 (folder 2 of 2)
  James M. Lawson – July 8, 1970 (folder 1 of 2)
  James M. Lawson – July 8, 1970 (folder 2 of 2)
  James M. Lawson – May 25, 1972
  James M. Lawson – Oral History Release – May 25, 1972
  Correspondence – Incoming -1998
  Newspaper Clippings – 1997-1998
- Civil Rights – Memphis Sanitation Strike – Miscellaneous – Box 47
  - Correspondence – Incoming – April 1968
  - Correspondence – Incoming – 1969
  - Correspondence – Incoming Poor Peoples Campaign – 1968
  - African Methodist Episcopal Church – January 1968
  - Citizens Commission to aid Public Works – 1968
  - Communism in Memphis – Correspondence – Incoming – 1968
  - Communism in Memphis – Correspondence – Incoming – 1969
  - Communism in Memphis – Miscellaneous – 1968-1969
  - Court Transcript – James M. Lawson - April 4, 1968
  - Downtown Business – Goldsmith – brochure – n.d.
  - From the Pastor’s Desk – 1968
  - King Assassination Leads – April 1968
  - Local 1733 – “Five Years Later” – 1973
  - Martin Luther King Memorial March – April 8, 1968
  - Martin Luther King Memorial March – April 4, 1969
  - Memorial for Martin Luther King – Platform Guest – n.d.
  - Memphis Memorial Service for Martin Luther King – April 12, 1968
  - Memphis City Council Resolutions – February 1968
  - Memphis Improvement Project – n.d.
  - Newsletter – “The Memphis Public Employee” – March 1971
  - Newspaper Clippings – March 1968
  - Newspaper Clippings – 1969
  - Notes – February 1968
  - Police Grievances – 1967-1969
  - Program – Memphis Cares – 1968
  - Program – March and Service of Celebration – January 1969
  - Remarks – Hubert H. Humphrey – April 1968
  - Report – Southern Regional Council – “In Memphis: More than a Garbage Strike” – 1968
  - Seminar on Community Organization – Presentation by Maulana Ron Karenga – June 22, 1968
  - Sermon – by James Lawson re: Martin Luther King – n.d.
  - Speech – by James Lawson – Tennessee Council on Human Relations – November 1968
  - Statement – Jacques Wilmore – February 24,1968
  - Statement – Albert Haines – April 8, 1968
  - Statement – Floyd Newsum – April 11, 1968
  - Statement – N. E. Wallace – April 12, 1968
  - Statement – Audrey Branch – April 13, 1968
  - Statement – Grace Walden – n.d.
  - Statement – Coy Love – n.d.
  - Study – Racial Negotiations—The Memphis Case by Ray Marshall and Arvil Van Adams – September 1969
  - WMC-TV Program “Can You Hear Me Now” – April 1969
- Civil Rights – Memphis Sanitation Strike – Box 48
  - Correspondence – Incoming - 1967
  - Correspondence – Incoming – January 1968
  - Correspondence – Incoming – February 1968
  - Correspondence – Incoming – March 1968
  - Correspondence – Incoming – May 1968
  - Correspondence – Incoming – September 1968
  - Correspondence – Incoming – October 1968
  - Correspondence – Incoming – n.d.
  - Correspondence – Incoming – Hate Mail – n.d.
  - Magazine Article – May 1968
  - Newspaper Article – Draft – November 1969
  - Newspaper Clippings – February 1968
  - Newspaper Clippings – April 1968
  - Newspaper Clippings – May 1968
  - Newspaper Clippings – February 1969
  - Newspaper Clippings – n.d.
  - Press Release – April 1968
  - Writings - “The Memphis Riot” – Some Eye-Witness Accounts of Events in Memphis, March 28-April 1, 1968 – assembled by Michael P. Johnson – May 14, 1968 (2 copies)
  - Writings – “King’s Last Spectacle” by David L. Mays – March 11, 1969
- Organizations – Fellowship of Reconciliation (FOR) – Box 36
  - Fellowship of Reconciliation – Correspondence – Incoming – 1950
  - Fellowship of Reconciliation – Correspondence – Incoming – 1952
  - Fellowship of Reconciliation – Correspondence – Incoming – March -June, 1958
  - Fellowship of Reconciliation – Correspondence – Incoming – July-December 1958
  - Fellowship of Reconciliation – Correspondence – Incoming – January-June, 1959
  - Fellowship of Reconciliation – Correspondence – Incoming – July-December, 1959
  - Fellowship of Reconciliation – Correspondence – Incoming – January-March, 1960
  - Fellowship of Reconciliation – Correspondence – Incoming – April-June, 1960
  - Fellowship of Reconciliation – Correspondence – Incoming – July-December, 1960
  - Fellowship of Reconciliation – Correspondence – Incoming – 1961
  - Fellowship of Reconciliation – Correspondence – Incoming – 1962
  - Fellowship of Reconciliation – Correspondence – Incoming – 1963-1966
  - Fellowship of Reconciliation – Correspondence – Incoming – 1972-1975
  - Fellowship of Reconciliation – Correspondence – Incoming – 1996
  - Fellowship of Reconciliation – Correspondence – Incoming - 1997
  - Fellowship of Reconciliation – Correspondence – Incoming – 1998
  - Fellowship of Reconciliation - Correspondence – Incoming – 1999
  - Fellowship of Reconciliation – Correspondence – Incoming – n.d.
  - Fellowship of Reconciliation – Correspondence – Outgoing – January-June, 1958
  - Fellowship of Reconciliation – Correspondence – Outgoing – June-December, 1958
  - Fellowship of Reconciliation – Correspondence – Outgoing – January-June, 1959
  - Fellowship of Reconciliation – Correspondence – Outgoing – July-December, 1959
  - Fellowship of Reconciliation – Correspondence – Outgoing – 1960
  - Fellowship of Reconciliation – Correspondence – Outgoing – 1961
  - Fellowship of Reconciliation – Correspondence – Outgoing – 1962
  - Fellowship of Reconciliation – Correspondence – Outgoing – n.d.
  - Fellowship of Reconciliation – Abortion Discussion – 1990-1999
  - Fellowship of Reconciliation – “Alternatives” – Discussion Guide – n.d.
  - Fellowship of Reconciliation – Americans For South African Resistance – 1953
  - Fellowship of Reconciliation – “The Basis and Power of Love” – 1959
  - Fellowship of Reconciliation – Amended Draft Bibliography on War, Pacifism, Nonviolence and Related Studies – 1959
  - Fellowship of Reconciliation – Biographies of National Council Members – 1997
  - Fellowship of Reconciliation – Brochures – n.d.
  - Fellowship of Reconciliation – “A Call For Racial Dialogue and Reconciliation” – 1989-1996
  - Fellowship of Reconciliation – Celebrating Richard Deats 25th Year – 1996
  - Fellowship of Reconciliation – Newspaper Clippings – 1959
  - Fellowship of Reconciliation – Newspaper Clippings – 1963
  - Fellowship of Reconciliation – Newspaper Clippings – 1995
  - Fellowship of Reconciliation – Newspaper Clippings – 1997
  - Fellowship of Reconciliation – Newspaper Clippings – 1998
- Organizations – Fellowship of Reconciliation (FOR) – Box 37
  - Fellowship of Reconciliation – Newsletter – ‘Current Issues” – 1960
  - Fellowship of Reconciliation – Newsletter – “Current Issues” _ 1961